acslaw.org 2004-12-07

# American Constitution Society

---  
Shop  
  | 

## American Constitution Society for Law and Policy  
Privacy Policy

We're glad you looked here. The American Constitution Society is sensitive to online privacy concerns. Among our organization's central goals is the protection of individual rights and liberties, including privacy.

**Browser information collected on the website**

As with any website operator, ACS analyzes our website logs to improve the value of our website. The firm that provides our Internet hosting reports to us about browser accesses to our site. This information includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect or track any Internet users' personally identifiable information.

**Privacy of our e-mail lists**

ACS maintains e-mail lists to keep interested parties informed about various activities of our organization. We do not share the e-mail addresses on our lists with outside organizations. 

**Cookies**

ACS does not use "cookies" (small data files placed on a user's computer by a server) to collect personal information on visitors to its website. 

**Collection and use of personally identifiable information**

At our site you can join or contribute to ACS, and in the process of doing so you may be requested to provide your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, and biographical information such as your place of employment and educational background.

ACS does not sell or otherwise disclose such personal information outside our organization. ACS, like most nonprofit organizations, does obtain the names of potential new members or attendees at our events by obtaining membership lists or subscriber lists of like-minded organizations and publications. Sometimes, instead of paying a rental fee for such lists, ACS might exchange its list with that of another organization. In such cases, your name and mailing address (but not any other information about you) might be exchanged with another organization.

|
